Agnes Geller

Crawley RH10 7SN

Phone: 07546371504 | Email: agnesgeller@cyberanalys.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/agnes-geller-209a992b9/ GitHub: https://github.com/AgnesGeller Portfolio: https://github.io/Bootstrap-Portfolio/

Personable and passionate Front -End Web Developer with a background in Logistics and Supply Chain Management with Front- End Web Developer Certificate from the EDx Bootcamp. Skills in application programming interfaces (APIs), user experience design, and building and deploying modern web applications. I have indemand skills through a market-driven curriculum that includes HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, React.js, Node. Collaborate and work with a team while solving problems in high-stress environments. An articulate individual enjoys connecting with co-workers and is passionate about building applications that assist everyday people to make their lives easier.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

Technical Languages: HTML, JavaScript, CSS, UX, Git, GitHub, Information architecture, User experience design, Modern front-end frameworks, Structuring, positioning, and optimisation of web page content, React.js, Netlify Developing with APIs, JavaScript framework, DOM manipulation, Web-based applications, Data extraction and retrieval, Git, GitHub, jQuery, RESTful compliant Network.

PROJECTS:

Project Name: HabitUI - Where Tracking Meets Triumph!

Link to GitHub: https://github.com/jonnoclifford/habitui

Link to Deployed Project: https://jonnoclifford.github.io/habitui/

Summary: The project is a web application named "HabitUI." It is a habit tracking and management tool, featuring sections for inspirational quotes, habit tracking, weather at their chosen location and a joke generator. Users can add, track, and delete habits, view their progress on a chart, and get a random joke. User information stored in local Storage so the user can return to the app over a period to track their progress.

Tools / languages used:

Bootstrap 4.0.0: A front-end framework for responsive and mobile-first web development. It is use for styling and layout components.

JavaScript (Vanilla): The primary scripting language for client-side interactions. It interacts with the DOM, fetches data, and manages user actions.

Chart.js: A JavaScript library for creating interactive charts. It used to visualize habit tracking progress with a bar chart.

jQuery: A fast and concise JavaScript library for simplifying DOM manipulations and AJAX requests. Used for managing events, making AJAX calls, and manipulating the DOM.

API Application:

Major summative project, collaborating in groups to execute against specific design specifications. Write an API-powered web application that pulls data from multiple sources in a creative way. Work as part of a collaborative project team to apply agile development methodologies. Prepare a professional presentation and repository README for the project. Explain and execute Git branching workflow. Resolve merge conflicts.

Experience:

EasyJet DHL London Gatwick Airport, Check in Agent, Passenger Service Officer 2023 London Gatwick Airport

Validating customer's documentation for travel. Processing customers for boarding.

Processing customers using manual and automated systems. Assisting customers during disruption. Ensuring compliance in both airline and airport policies.

Amazon and Yodel Delivery Organizer, Management of Cleaning services 2013-2022 Crawley West Sussex

During that time, I have run my own delivery and cleaning service businesses.

G & G High Quality Kft. Trucker and Frigo DSV Gmbh Freight Forwarder for EU 2005-2011 Budapest Hungary

As a company owner I was responsible for all shipping activities, managing the company & staff also TimoCom and making invoices. Marketing, negotiations and looking for new partner companies were also big part of my duties.

Ibusz Logistics Centre t, 1118 Budapest, Hungary, Transport Organizer 2003- 2005

Responsible for freight forwarding onto the road in EU.

Generating invoices, translating for correspondence and being first point of contact for all transport activities were part of my everyday tasks.

EDUCATION:

Front End Web Development Boot Camp Certificate: EDx Bootcamp

An intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node.js, APIs, and ReactJS. *Git, GitHub, Slack, Netlify*

Certification: Front End Web Developer

2024 – Front-End Web Developer Edx Bootcamp Certificate, HTML, JavaScript, CSS, UX. Git, GitHub, Information architecture, User experience design, Modern front-end frameworks, Structuring, positioning, and optimisation of web page content, React.js, Netlify Developing with APIs, JavaScript framework, DOM manipulation, Web-based applications, Data extraction and retrieval, Git, GitHub, jQuery, RESTful compliant Network

2023 – NCFE Level 2 Principle of Coding

2023 - NCFE Level 2 Principle of Cyber Security

2023 – UK National Aviation Security Training Programme

2023 – LGW Airside Safety Awareness

2023 – DHL Supply Chain

2018 - Complementary Therapies and Practitioner Diploma in Swedish Massage Therapy, y Edinburgh Napier University

Higher Education:

2008 Karoli Gaspar Calvinistic University of Law, Budapest, Hungary2005 Currency Exchange manager qualification, Budapest, Hungary2002 Logistics and Freight Forwarding, Supply Chain Management College of Foreign Trade